24x7tube.com 2010-11-25

# We take your privacy seriously at Magnify.net

Our full Privacy Policy describes how we treat personal information when you use our service. The following is a "short version" of our privacy practices:

#### Personal information

Magnify.net asks for some personal information when you sign up to use our platform, including your email address and a password, which is used to protect your account from unauthorized access.

In addition to publishing your video channel, you may also provide additional profile information, such as a photo, email, location, etc. You can edit your profile at any time on your site's administration page.

Magnify.net servers automatically record information about your use of the service, such as when you use Magnfiy.net, the frequency of your visits, the number of videos on your site, the number of members, and storage usage. Information displayed or clicked in the Magnify.net interface (including UI elements, settings, and other information) is also recorded.

#### Uses

Magnify.net stores and maintains your account information and copies of your users review posts and comments, in order to provide the service.

Magnify.net adheres to the Digital Millennium Copyright Act (DMCA) and we request that all users of our platform also adhere to this legislation. For more information about the DMCA see their site.

#### Your choices

You can change your Magnify.net account settings, including your profile information, at any time in the Account section of the administration page. 

You can edit the sites, keywords and schedule for delivering videos.

You can edit the page design, color, header, category, and keywords for your site(s) at any time.

If you abandon your site for over 90 days we will remove all videos and links from public view. Because of the way we maintain this service, residual copies of your profile information and other information associated with your account may remain on back-up media.

#### More information

For more information about our privacy practices, go to our full privacy policy.

Further information about Magnify.net is available in our About or Contact Us pages.

If you have additional questions, please feel free to contact us mediamagnify.net.

### About Us

### Explore

### Contact

### Service Terms

« Privacy Policy
